[
  {
    "question": "What famous speaker warmed the Greeks that King Philip II, the Macedonian King was a threat to Greek Freedom?",
    "choice1": "Demosthenes",
    "choice2": "Granicus",
    "choice3": "Darius",
    "choice4": "Fever",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Alexander and his army of 40,000 soldiers defeated the Persians at the Battle of ___________",
    "choice1": "Demosthenes",
    "choice2": "Granicus",
    "choice3": "Darius",
    "choice4": "Fever",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Alexander's main enemy was _________, the King of the Persians",
    "choice1": "Demosthenes",
    "choice2": "Granicus",
    "choice3": "Darius",
    "choice4": "Fever",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Alexander died because of his wounds and _________",
    "choice1": "Demosthenes",
    "choice2": "Granicus",
    "choice3": "Darius",
    "choice4": "Fever",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "After his death, Alexander's empire was __________ because his generals fought one another",
    "choice1": "divided",
    "choice2": "Greek",
    "choice3": "Legacy",
    "choice4": "Darius",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Hellenistic Kings wanted government business conducted in the _____________ language",
    "choice1": "divided",
    "choice2": "Greek",
    "choice3": "Legacy",
    "choice4": "Darius",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What a person leaves behind when they die is called their _________",
    "choice1": "divided",
    "choice2": "Greek",
    "choice3": "Legacy",
    "choice4": "Darius",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the King of the Persians?",
    "choice1": "divided",
    "choice2": "Greek",
    "choice3": "Legacy",
    "choice4": "Darius",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "part of an army  in which the soldiers ride horses",
    "choice1": "Calvary",
    "choice2": "Hellenistic Era",
    "choice3": "wounds",
    "choice4": "King Philip II",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "the time period following the death of Alexander during which Greek culture spread through the known world",
   "choice1": "Calvary",
    "choice2": "Hellenistic Era",
    "choice3": "wounds",
    "choice4": "King Philip II",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Alexander died because of his ___________ and fever",
    "choice1": "Calvary",
    "choice2": "Hellenistic Era",
    "choice3": "wounds",
    "choice4": "King Philip II",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the Macedonian King?",
    "choice1": "Calvary",
    "choice2": "Hellenistic Era",
    "choice3": "wounds",
    "choice4": "King Philip II",
    "answer": 4
  }
 ]
